/* 1 */
{
    "_id" : ObjectId("5abc00873da127f248ae3fb8"),
    "question" : "Which came first, C or C++?",
    "answer" : "C",
    "author" : "reifx049"
}

/* 2 */
{
    "_id" : ObjectId("5abc01573da127f248ae400c"),
    "question" : "Java and Python are ______-oriented languages",
    "answer" : "object-oriented languaged",
    "author" : "reifx049"
}

/* 3 */
{
    "_id" : ObjectId("5ac62f203da127f248b05cf5"),
    "question" : "What number does an array's index start at?",
    "answer" : "0",
    "author" : "reifx049"
}

/* 4 */
{
    "_id" : ObjectId("5ac6301a3da127f248b05d42"),
    "question" : "Translate the following binary: 01 10 11",
    "answer" : "1 2 3",
    "author" : "reifx049"
}

/* 5 */
{
    "_id" : ObjectId("5ad6126e2f7704cf3c0f78fc"),
    "question" : "How does a deadlock occur in threads?",
    "answer" : "Deadlocks occur if no thread can proceed due to them both waiting for eachother.",
    "author" : "5ad6108e2f7704cf3c0f78f9",
    "__v" : 0
}

/* 6 */
{
    "_id" : ObjectId("5ad612df2f7704cf3c0f78fd"),
    "question" : "What are the three stages of stream processing?\r\n",
    "answer" : "generation, transformation, termination",
    "author" : "5ad6108e2f7704cf3c0f78f9",
    "__v" : 0
}

/* 7 */
{
    "_id" : ObjectId("5ad613012f7704cf3c0f78fe"),
    "question" : "What is the the purpose of a hash table?",
    "answer" : "Hash tables are an efficient structure for implementing dictionary operations. A good hash\r\nfunction will minimize collisions (data hashing to the same index) as much as possible.",
    "author" : "5ad6108e2f7704cf3c0f78f9",
    "__v" : 0
}

/* 8 */
{
    "_id" : ObjectId("5ad7ad5547d3edd04ed4b03f"),
    "question" : "What is the average complexity of bubble sort?",
    "answer" : "O(n^2)",
    "author" : "5ad7acf647d3edd04ed4b03c",
    "__v" : 0
}

/* 9 */
{
    "_id" : ObjectId("5ad7adc147d3edd04ed4b044"),
    "question" : "What does SQL stand for?",
    "answer" : "Structured Query Language",
    "author" : "5ad610ee2f7704cf3c0f78fa",
    "__v" : 0
}

/* 10 */
{
    "_id" : ObjectId("5ad7afe247d3edd04ed4b045"),
    "question" : "What is the average performance of Quicksort.",
    "answer" : "O(nlogn)",
    "author" : "5ad7acf647d3edd04ed4b03c",
    "__v" : 0
}

/* 11 */
{
    "_id" : ObjectId("5ad7b3ae47d3edd04ed4b046"),
    "question" : "Define encapsulation",
    "answer" : "Separating how a class's data is represented from how the class is used",
    "author" : "5ad7aac947d3edd04ed4b030",
    "__v" : 0
}

/* 12 */
{
    "_id" : ObjectId("5ad7b3c447d3edd04ed4b047"),
    "question" : "Define abstraction",
    "answer" : "Hiding the details of how a class is implemented from users of the class",
    "author" : "5ad7aac947d3edd04ed4b030",
    "__v" : 0
}

/* 13 */
{
    "_id" : ObjectId("5ad7b3ea47d3edd04ed4b048"),
    "question" : "Define polymorphism",
    "answer" : "Using interface-typed variables so that code can have different behavior depending on the types of objects they reference at run-time",
    "author" : "5ad7aac947d3edd04ed4b030",
    "__v" : 0
}

/* 14 */
{
    "_id" : ObjectId("5ad7b42147d3edd04ed4b049"),
    "question" : "What mechanism does Java use for passing both primitive and object reference parameter types?",
    "answer" : "Call by value (parameter copying)",
    "author" : "5ad7aac947d3edd04ed4b030",
    "__v" : 0
}

/* 15 */
{
    "_id" : ObjectId("5ad7b44347d3edd04ed4b04a"),
    "question" : "Why must arithmetic methods like square root be referred to in Java like Math.sqrt instead of just sqrt?",
    "answer" : "Because they are static methods and thus are called without an implicit parameter.",
    "author" : "5ad7aac947d3edd04ed4b030",
    "__v" : 0
}

/* 16 */
{
    "_id" : ObjectId("5ad7b46347d3edd04ed4b04b"),
    "question" : "What is the difference between checked and unchecked exceptions in Java?",
    "answer" : "Checked exception conditions are detected at compile time and the programmer is forced to handle or throw them. Unchecked exception conditions are not detected.",
    "author" : "5ad7aac947d3edd04ed4b030",
    "__v" : 0
}

/* 17 */
{
    "_id" : ObjectId("5ad7b49c47d3edd04ed4b04c"),
    "question" : "Describe the class relationship known as Aggregation.",
    "answer" : "When a class object \"has\" an object of another class type as part of its state: the class has an instance field that is another class type or a collection of another class type",
    "author" : "5ad7aac947d3edd04ed4b030",
    "__v" : 0
}

/* 18 */
{
    "_id" : ObjectId("5ad7b4cf47d3edd04ed4b04d"),
    "question" : "Describe the class relationship known as Inheritance.",
    "answer" : "When an object that is an instance of one class \"is\" also an instance of another: the class is a subclass of, or extends, the other",
    "author" : "5ad7aac947d3edd04ed4b030",
    "__v" : 0
}

/* 19 */
{
    "_id" : ObjectId("5ad7b4ec47d3edd04ed4b04e"),
    "question" : "Describe the Implementation relationship that holds between a class and an interface",
    "answer" : "When a class provides definitions (implementations) for the methods whose signatures are specified in the interface.",
    "author" : "5ad7aac947d3edd04ed4b030",
    "__v" : 0
}

/* 20 */
{
    "_id" : ObjectId("5ad7b54c47d3edd04ed4b04f"),
    "question" : "Name and describe five criteria used to analyze the quality of an interface to a class.",
    "answer" : "Cohesion: all operations provided by the interface revolve around a common purpose\r\nCompleteness: all operations that make sense for the class are supported by the interface\r\nConvenience: the interface makes common tasks simple\r\nClarity: the interface does not confuse programmers\r\nConsistency: the operations for an interface have matching names, parameters, return values, and behavior",
    "author" : "5ad7aac947d3edd04ed4b030",
    "__v" : 0
}

/* 21 */
{
    "_id" : ObjectId("5ad7b59647d3edd04ed4b050"),
    "question" : "The equals method is defined in java.lang.Object, so it is inherited by all classes. Why is it a good idea to override it?",
    "answer" : "The inherited equals only checks for object identity (this == other), while object equality usually asks whether two separate objects have the same state",
    "author" : "5ad7aac947d3edd04ed4b030",
    "__v" : 0
}

/* 22 */
{
    "_id" : ObjectId("5ad7b5be47d3edd04ed4b051"),
    "question" : "What should every overridden equals method do before it compares two objects' state?",
    "answer" : "Check to make sure the class of the other object is the same as the class of this object, using getClass, then cast the other object to this object's class",
    "author" : "5ad7aac947d3edd04ed4b030",
    "__v" : 0
}

/* 23 */
{
    "_id" : ObjectId("5ad7b5db47d3edd04ed4b052"),
    "question" : "The toString method is defined in java.lang.Object, so it is inherited by all classes. Why is it a good idea to override it?",
    "answer" : "The inherited toString only returns the string representation of the object's class and memory location. Since toString is often used for debugging, this behavior is of limited value.",
    "author" : "5ad7aac947d3edd04ed4b030",
    "__v" : 0
}

/* 24 */
{
    "_id" : ObjectId("5ad7b65047d3edd04ed4b053"),
    "question" : "Describe Java's reflection capability.",
    "answer" : "Reflection is the ability of a running program to find out about its objects and classes, including details about constructors, methods, and fields.",
    "author" : "5ad7aac947d3edd04ed4b030",
    "__v" : 0
}

/* 25 */
{
    "_id" : ObjectId("5ad7b6b247d3edd04ed4b054"),
    "question" : "What is a functional interface?",
    "answer" : "An interface with exactly one abstract (that is, non-default and non-static) method",
    "author" : "5ad7aac947d3edd04ed4b030",
    "__v" : 0
}

/* 26 */
{
    "_id" : ObjectId("5ad7b6c547d3edd04ed4b055"),
    "question" : "Generally, what is a lambda expression in Java 8?",
    "answer" : "A parameterized piece of code that can be passed around and executed",
    "author" : "5ad7aac947d3edd04ed4b030",
    "__v" : 0
}

/* 27 */
{
    "_id" : ObjectId("5ad7b6de47d3edd04ed4b056"),
    "question" : "Is a lambda expression an object?",
    "answer" : "No, it is best understood as an anonymous function",
    "author" : "5ad7aac947d3edd04ed4b030",
    "__v" : 0
}

/* 28 */
{
    "_id" : ObjectId("5ad7b6f747d3edd04ed4b057"),
    "question" : "Where can a lambda expression be used in a program?",
    "answer" : "Any place where an instance of a class implementing a functional interface is expected",
    "author" : "5ad7aac947d3edd04ed4b030",
    "__v" : 0
}

/* 29 */
{
    "_id" : ObjectId("5ad7b72347d3edd04ed4b058"),
    "question" : "To create a GUI using JavaFX, which class must be extended?",
    "answer" : "The Application class, in the package javafx.application",
    "author" : "5ad7aac947d3edd04ed4b030",
    "__v" : 0
}

/* 30 */
{
    "_id" : ObjectId("5ad8b0b847d3edd04ed4b062"),
    "question" : "Object-oriented programming is based on the concept of objects. Name some characteristics of an object",
    "answer" : "Objects contain data called attributes, and use methods to access and modify memory of the object",
    "author" : "5ad55f842f7704cf3c0f78f7",
    "__v" : 0
}

/* 31 */
{
    "_id" : ObjectId("5ad8b13247d3edd04ed4b063"),
    "question" : "Python, Ruby, Scala, and JADE are what kind of objected-oriented language?",
    "answer" : "Pure; these languages treat everything as an object",
    "author" : "5ad55f842f7704cf3c0f78f7",
    "__v" : 0
}

/* 32 */
{
    "_id" : ObjectId("5ad8b1c547d3edd04ed4b064"),
    "question" : "What is github?",
    "answer" : "Github is a collaborative program that allows a group to build software and track each and every change in their code.",
    "author" : "5ad55f842f7704cf3c0f78f7",
    "__v" : 0
}

/* 33 */
{
    "_id" : ObjectId("5ad8b28847d3edd04ed4b065"),
    "question" : "What is the size(in bits) of an integer variable?",
    "answer" : "32 bits",
    "author" : "5ad55f842f7704cf3c0f78f7",
    "__v" : 0
}

/* 34 */
{
    "_id" : ObjectId("5ad8b29d47d3edd04ed4b066"),
    "question" : "What is the size(in bits) of an double variable?",
    "answer" : "64 bits",
    "author" : "5ad55f842f7704cf3c0f78f7",
    "__v" : 0
}

/* 35 */
{
    "_id" : ObjectId("5ad8b2b447d3edd04ed4b067"),
    "question" : "What is the size(in bits) of an float variable?",
    "answer" : "32",
    "author" : "5ad55f842f7704cf3c0f78f7",
    "__v" : 0
}

/* 36 */
{
    "_id" : ObjectId("5ad8b2e147d3edd04ed4b068"),
    "question" : "What is the size(in bits) of an char variable?",
    "answer" : "16 bits",
    "author" : "5ad55f842f7704cf3c0f78f7",
    "__v" : 0
}

/* 37 */
{
    "_id" : ObjectId("5ada853b47d3edd04ed4b069"),
    "question" : "How does a binary search algorithm work?",
    "answer" : "The list is halved until the item is found.",
    "author" : "5ad6108e2f7704cf3c0f78f9",
    "__v" : 0
}

/* 38 */
{
    "_id" : ObjectId("5ada856f47d3edd04ed4b06a"),
    "question" : "What is encryption?",
    "answer" : "Process of changing data so that it cannot be read without a decryption key.",
    "author" : "5ad6108e2f7704cf3c0f78f9",
    "__v" : 0
}

/* 39 */
{
    "_id" : ObjectId("5ada85b547d3edd04ed4b06b"),
    "question" : "What is the exact definition of an integer, and what numbers can and cannot be integers?",
    "answer" : "An integer can only be a number that is positive or negative, with no decimal points. Examples: 1, -5, 123.",
    "author" : "5ad6108e2f7704cf3c0f78f9",
    "__v" : 0
}

/* 40 */
{
    "_id" : ObjectId("5ada865547d3edd04ed4b06c"),
    "question" : "What data structure  accesses data LIFO (Last in first out)? ",
    "answer" : "Stack",
    "author" : "5ad6108e2f7704cf3c0f78f9",
    "__v" : 0
}

/* 41 */
{
    "_id" : ObjectId("5ada869347d3edd04ed4b06d"),
    "question" : "What is a reference?",
    "answer" : "A pointer to the memory location, or address of an object",
    "author" : "5ad6108e2f7704cf3c0f78f9",
    "__v" : 0
}

/* 42 */
{
    "_id" : ObjectId("5ada86bc47d3edd04ed4b06e"),
    "question" : "What data structure accesses data FIFO (First in first out)",
    "answer" : "Queue",
    "author" : "5ad6108e2f7704cf3c0f78f9",
    "__v" : 0
}

/* 43 */
{
    "_id" : ObjectId("5ada86ca47d3edd04ed4b06f"),
    "question" : "What data structure randomly accesses data?",
    "answer" : "Bag",
    "author" : "5ad6108e2f7704cf3c0f78f9",
    "__v" : 0
}

/* 44 */
{
    "_id" : ObjectId("5ada88fa47d3edd04ed4b070"),
    "question" : "What does hertz measure?",
    "answer" : "Speed of a computer's internal clock, or the measure of CPU speed in cycles per second.",
    "author" : "5ad6108e2f7704cf3c0f78f9",
    "__v" : 0
}

/* 45 */
{
    "_id" : ObjectId("5ada892e47d3edd04ed4b071"),
    "question" : "What does a compiler do?",
    "answer" : "Converts high level languages, like java, into low level machine language (1's and 0's).",
    "author" : "5ad6108e2f7704cf3c0f78f9",
    "__v" : 0
}

/* 46 */
{
    "_id" : ObjectId("5ada8a3a47d3edd04ed4b072"),
    "question" : "What is the notation used to determine the efficiencies of algorithms and data structures?",
    "answer" : "Big O notation",
    "author" : "5ad6108e2f7704cf3c0f78f9",
    "__v" : 0
}

/* 47 */
{
    "_id" : ObjectId("5adcc1e047d3edd04ed4b073"),
    "question" : "Define a primary key is database management systems.",
    "answer" : "special relational database table column  designated to uniquely identify all table records",
    "author" : "5ad610ee2f7704cf3c0f78fa",
    "__v" : 0
}

/* 48 */
{
    "_id" : ObjectId("5adcc21447d3edd04ed4b074"),
    "question" : "What is the topmost node of a binary tree called?",
    "answer" : "Root",
    "author" : "5ad610ee2f7704cf3c0f78fa",
    "__v" : 0
}

/* 49 */
{
    "_id" : ObjectId("5adcc2b747d3edd04ed4b075"),
    "question" : "What are elements in binary trees that have no children?",
    "answer" : "Leaves",
    "author" : "5ad610ee2f7704cf3c0f78fa",
    "__v" : 0
}

/* 50 */
{
    "_id" : ObjectId("5adcc57d47d3edd04ed4b076"),
    "question" : "What does the WHERE clause do in an SQL statement?",
    "answer" : "Filters the records & used to only extract records that fulfill a condition",
    "author" : "5ad610ee2f7704cf3c0f78fa",
    "__v" : 0
}